Edward 40 hands. Sorry, it's just people are
complaining too bad, you know, they want to
know if you guys can maybe try tuning up again
or no play on beat and just do it right
? No. Alright, let's stop fooling around and
turn this band into a lean mean Mom jeans,
revenge machine. Yeah. Mom jeans. What do
you want me to say? It's never going away
because I'm stuck on you. Like the smell of
cigarettes on your flower dress. I want you under
my fingernails, I want you in my sleeping in
my dreams. I wake up spooning my pillow,
sweaty hands, but please don't tell your friends now
. I'm addicted to cigarettes at first I didn't let
myself inhale, but smoke got through and so did
you. And now every burn hole smells like home
and I know it's killing me, but that still
won't stop me because now we smell the same,
but you still kill me faster. I don't mind
that you lie sometimes because I lie to guess.
I'm just like you, I don't mind that you
lie sometimes because I lie to guess I'm just like
you. I don't mind that you lie sometimes because
I lie to guess I'm just like you, I
don't mind that you lie sometimes because I lie to
you. I guess I'm just like you, I
don't mind that you lie sometimes because you to guess
I'm just like you